<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">appVote-Sainorum</string>
    <string name="loginEnviar">Log in</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="large_text">Text largo</string>
    <string name="loginInfo">You need to log in to our app to be able to create a vote</string>
    <string name="loginInfoRegister">Enter your email and password to log in</string>
    <string name="forgotPassword">Have you forgotten the password?</string>
    <string name="option">Options:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_privacy_policies">privacyPolicies</string>
    <string name="loginNewCount">Create new account</string>
    <string name="enterYourEmail">Enter your email</string>
    <string name="sendValidateEmail">Send validation email</string>
    <string name="acceptPrivacyPolicies">I accept the Privacy Policies</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicies">" Privacy policies"</string>
    <string name="acceptSendOferts">I want to receive information about offers and news</string>
    <string name="newPoll">Create poll</string>
    <string name="joinPoll">Join a vote</string>
    <string name="joinResultPoll">"See survey result "</string>
    <string name="updatePassword">Update password</string>
    <string name="saveChanges">Save changes</string>
    <string name="enterPollId">Enter the id of the vote</string>
    <string name="joinRandomPoll">"Join a Random vote "</string>
    <string name="joinResultRandomPoll">View a random poll</string>
    <string name="typePoll">Type of poll:</string>
    <string name="writeQuestion">Write your question</string>
    <string name="enterYourOption">Enter your option</string>
    <string name="addOptionPoll">Add option to vote</string>
    <string name="bigGoogle">GOOGLE</string>
    <string name="logIn">Log in</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="checkIn">Check in</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="loginEmail">email@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="loginPassword">Password</string>
    <string name="repeatPassword">Repeat Password</string>
    <string name="leave">Leave</string>
    <string name="privacyPoliciesTitle">Privacy Policies</string>
    <string name="privacyPoliciesText1">Your privacy is important to us. It is sainerum\'s policy to respect your privacy and comply with any laws and\n        applicable regulation with respect to any personal information that we may collect about you.</string>
    <string name="privacyPoliciesText2">This policy is effective as of November 1, 2021 and was last updated on November 1, 2021</string>
    <string name="logDataTitle">Data register</string>
    <string name="logDataText1">When you visit our website, our servers may automatically record the standard data provided\n        by your web browser. It may include the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your device, the type and version of your browser, the\n        pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time you spend on each page, other details about your visit and the technical details that occur\n        in along with any errors you may find.</string>
    <string name="logDataText2">Please note that while this information may not itself be personally identifiable,\n        It can be combined with other data to personally identify individual persons.</string>
    <string name="userInformationTitle">Information collection and use</string>
    <string name="userInformationText1">We may collect personal information from you when you perform any of the following actions on our website:</string>
    <string name="userInformationText2">Please use a mobile device or a web browser to access our content.\nContact us by email, social media or any similar technology.\nWhen you mention us on social media.</string>
    <string name="userInformationText3">We may collect, retain, use and disclose information for the following purposes, and personal information will no longer be processed in a way that is incompatible with these purposes:</string>
    <string name="userInformationText4">Please note that we may combine the information we collect about you with general information or research data that we receive from other reliable sources.</string>
    <string name="securityInformationTitle">Security of your personal information</string>
    <string name="securityInformationText1">When we collect and process personal information, and while we retain this information, we will protect it within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.</string>
    <string name="securityInformationText2">Although we will do our best to protect the personal information you provide us, we advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure and no one can guarantee the absolute security of the data. We will comply with the laws that apply to us with respect to any data breach.</string>
    <string name="securityInformationText3">You are responsible for selecting any password and its general security level, ensuring the security of your own information within the limits of our services.</string>
    <string name="keepInformationTitle">How long do we store your personal information?</string>
    <string name="keepInformationText1">We keep your personal information only for as long as it is necessary. This period of time may depend on what we are using your information for, in accordance with this privacy policy. If your personal information is no longer needed, we will delete it or make it anonymous by removing all identifying details.</string>
    <string name="keepInformationText2">However, if necessary, we may retain your personal information for our fulfillment of a legal, accounting or reporting obligation or for archival purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical research purposes, or statistical purposes.</string>
    <string name="internationalInformationTitle">International transfer of personal information</string>
    <string name="internationalInformationText">The personal information that we collect is stored and / or processed where we or our partners, affiliates and third-party providers have facilities. Please note that the locations to which we store, process or transfer your personal information may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. If we transfer your personal information to third parties in other countries: (i) we will make those transfers in accordance with the requirements of applicable law; and (ii) we will protect the personal information transferred in accordance with this privacy policy.</string>
    <string name="informationControllingTitle">Rights and control over your personal information</string>
    <string name="informationControllingText1">It always reserves the right to withhold personal information from us, with the understanding that your experience on our website may be affected. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights over your personal information. If you provide us with personal information, you understand that we will collect, retain, use and disclose it in accordance with this privacy policy. You retain the right to request details of any personal information we hold about you.</string>
    <string name="informationControllingText2">If we receive personal information about you from a third party, we will protect it as set out in this privacy policy. If you are a third party who provides personal information about another person, you represent and warrant that you have the consent of that person to provide us with the personal information.</string>
    <string name="informationControllingText3">If you have previously agreed to our use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you can change your mind at any time. We will provide you with the ability to unsubscribe from our email database or opt out of receiving communications. Please note that we may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity.</string>
    <string name="informationControllingText4">If you believe that the information we hold about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, please contact us using the details provided in this privacy policy. We will take reasonable steps to correct any information that is found to be inaccurate, incomplete, misleading, or out of date.</string>
    <string name="informationControllingText5">If you believe that we have violated a relevant data protection law and you wish to make a complaint, please contact us using the details below and provide us with all the details of the alleged violation. We will investigate your complaint promptly and respond to you, in writing, outlining the outcome of our investigation and the steps we will take to address your complaint. You also have the right to contact a regulatory body or data protection authority regarding your complaint.</string>
    <string name="cookiesTitle">Use of Cookies</string>
    <string name="cookiesText">We use cookies to collect information about you and your activity on our site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our website stores on your computer and is accessed each time you visit it, so that we can understand how you use our site. This helps us deliver content to you based on the preferences you have specified.</string>
    <string name="limitsTitle">Limits of our policy</string>
    <string name="limitsText">Our website may have links to external sites that are not operated by us. Please note that we have no control over the content and policies of those sites, and we cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.</string>
    <string name="policityChangesTitle">Policy changes</string>
    <string name="policityChangesText1">At our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to reflect updates to our business processes, current acceptable practices, or legislative or regulatory changes. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post the changes here at the same link by which you are accessing this privacy policy.</string>
    <string name="policityChangesText2">If required by law, we will obtain your permission or give you the opportunity to opt-out or opt-out, as applicable, of any further use of your personal information.</string>
    <string name="contactUsTitle">Contact us</string>
    <string name="contactUsText1">For any questions or concerns regarding your privacy, you can contact us using the following details:</string>
    <string name="contactUsName">Daniel</string>
    <string name="contactUsCorreo">sainero2002dani.j@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="idOfPoll">Id of Poll:</string>
    <string name="sendResult">Send results</string>
    <string name="goToMain">Go to main</string>


</resources>